

SUMMARY

8A- Winnie House, Kalina Market, MUMBAI- 400098 +91-98929 86762 or +9196727 92727 mohitarora.j2ee@gmail.com

Full Stack Developer (Java) with 6 Years' experience in Angular JS, Spring Boot, Spring microservices, Hibernate, JPA, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Java/J2EE, Rabbit MQ, Kendo UI, Jenkins and Maven.

Successful background in development of Real Time Trade Monitoring platform for Equity/Forex, loan cycle platform, and multiple 3-tier based applications.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2015 - Present **ASSISTANT MANAGER**

Edelweiss Financial Services, Mumbai.

Responsible for handling team and development of multiple applications for finance related businesses/FinTech requirements. Delivered applications for Stock market trading business and NBFC domain.

2014 – 2015 **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

Pratham Software Pvt. Ltd., Jaipur.

Responsible for designing and developing set of significant components in BPM application, Created workflows for credit document data capture and developed a web application for publishing workflow data.

2013 - 2014 JAVA DEVELOPER

Midnight Oxygen Pvt. Ltd., Jaipur.

Responsible for development of multiple web based applications.

EDUCATION

2010 – 2013 MASTER OF COMPUTER APPLICATIONS Suresh Gyan Vihar University, *Jaipur*.

GPA - 8.38/10

2007 - 2010 BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATIONS

University of Rajasthan, Jaipur.

GPA - 67/100

AWARDS

Walking the extra mile - 2018

SKILLS

Programming/

Framework

Java/J2EE Angular JS

Spring-Boot

Spring Security/ Core

PL/SQL

JPA/Hibernate microservices

Database/Tools

PostgreSQL

MongoDB

MSSQL Server

Eclipse

Maven/Jenkins

JIRA/bitbucket

RabbitMQ

Languages

English

Hindi/Punjabi

PROJECTS

QUBER – Corporate Lending (SpringBoot/Java-J2EE/PostgreSQL/AngularJS)

ORION – Trade Monitoring (Spring/Java-J2EE/MongoDB)

SHARESPACE – Secure

Shared Data Management Tool (SpringBoot/Seclore/AngularJS /Java-J2EE)

CONNECT

linkedin.com/in/mohitaroralive